https://www.meadplant.com/privacy.shtml

Construction equipment suppliers including New & Reconditioned Generators, Axles, Gearboxes & Spare Parts
Lister Petter Powered Generators
Perkins Powered Generators (EU Models)
Perkins Powered Generators (Non-EU Export Models)
Privacy Policy
Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our services. This policy may change from time to time.
Who is collecting your information?
When you are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with the M.E.A.D. PLANT only.
With whom may your information be shared?
Your information will not be shared with any third party without your written consent.
The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, M.E.A.D. PLANT cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
What else you should know about your online privacy.
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in ads that you post or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.
Personal information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by sending an email to info@meadplant.com. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.
If you have any questions/comments about our privacy policy please contact us
Our terms and conditions are available upon request.
Main Agents for:
